[
  {"category":"MUSIC", "question":"Which artist has the highest streamed song on spotify", "answer":"Ed Sheeran"},
  {"category":"MUSIC", "question":"What is the most streamed song on spotify", "answer":"Blinding Light - The Weeknd"},
  {"category":"MUSIC", "question":"Who is considered the 'King of Pop'", "answer":"Michael Jackson"},
  {"category":"MUSIC", "question":"What dance did Michael Jackson popularize in 1983?", "answer":"The Moonwalk"},
  {"category":"MUSIC", "question":"What was Kanye West's third studio album", "answer":"Graduation"},
  {"category":"MUSIC", "question":"What card game appeared in a #1 Lady Gaga song", "answer":"Poker"},
  {"category":"MUSIC", "question":"Reggae originates from which Carribean island", "answer":"Jamaica"},
  {"category":"MUSIC", "question":"By what 4-letter name is U2s front man better known?", "answer":"Bono"},
  {"category":"MUSIC", "question":"Who wrote the lead single for the Bond movie No Time To Die", "answer":"Billie Eilish"},
  {"category":"MUSIC", "question":"What rock star is also a horror movie writer and director", "answer":"Rob Zombie"},
  {"category":"MUSIC", "question":"Which classic composer was deaf", "answer":"Beethoven"},
  {"category":"MUSIC", "question":"Which astronomer was namedropped in Queen's 'Bohemian Rhapsody'", "answer":"Galileo"},
  {"category":"MUSIC", "question":"Rapper Shawn Carter goes by what other name", "answer":"Jay-Z"},
  {"category":"MUSIC", "question":"What genre of music did Taylor Swift start in", "answer":"Country"},
  
  {"category":"CELEBRITIES", "question":"In 2021 Kanye West legally changed his name to what two letter letter name?", "answer":"Ye"},
  {"category":"CELEBRITIES", "question":"Which actor starred in 'Ghost Rider' and 'National Treasure'", "answer":"Nicholas Cage"},
  {"category":"CELEBRITIES", "question":"Which boxer was known as 'The People's Champion'", "answer":"Muhammad Ali"},

  {"category":"RELIGION", "question":"How many deadly sins are there", "answer":"7"},

  {"category":"SCIENCE", "question":"Which subatomic particle has a charge of -1", "answer":"Electron"},
  {"category":"SCIENCE", "question":"An involuntary contraction of the diaphragm is aka", "answer":"Hiccup"},
  {"category":"SCIENCE", "question":"What is the boiling point of water in celsius", "answer":"100 degrees"},
  {"category":"SCIENCE", "question":"What is the boiling point of milk in celsius", "answer":"100 degrees"},
  {"category":"SCIENCE", "question":"How many protons are in one hydrogen atom", "answer":"1"},
  {"category":"SCIENCE", "question":"What is the chemical formula for water", "answer":"H2O"},
  {"category":"SCIENCE", "question":"What gas gives fizzy drinks their fizz", "answer":"CO2"},

  {"category":"GEOGRAPHY", "question":"Area 51 is located in which US state", "answer":"Nevada"},
  {"category":"GEOGRAPHY", "question":"What is the largest US state", "answer":"Alaska"},
  {"category":"GEOGRAPHY", "question":"Which US State comes second alphabetically", "answer":"Alaska"},
  {"category":"GEOGRAPHY", "question":"What is the capital of Brazil", "answer":"Brasilia"},
  {"category":"GEOGRAPHY", "question":"What country has the most tornados per square mile", "answer":"The UK"},
  {"category":"GEOGRAPHY", "question":"What is the currency of India", "answer":"Rupees"},
  {"category":"GEOGRAPHY", "question":"Which two countries share the largest border", "answer":"US and Canada"},
  {"category":"GEOGRAPHY", "question":"In what country does the Cannes film festival take place", "answer":"France"},
  {"category":"GEOGRAPHY", "question":"Which city originally exported hotdogs to the US", "answer":"Orange"},
  {"category":"GEOGRAPHY", "question":"On what date is St Patrick's Day celebrated", "answer":"17th of March"},
  {"category":"GEOGRAPHY", "question":"14% of Americans could not identify which country on a map", "answer":"America"},
  {"category":"GEOGRAPHY", "question":"Which long, thin country spans over half of the South American west coast", "answer":"Chile"},
  
  {"category":"SPORTS", "question":"What shirt number does Ronaldo wear", "answer":"7"},
  {"category":"SPORTS", "question":"How many balls are on a pool table at the start of the game", "answer":"16"},
  {"category":"SPORTS", "question":"What is the ball used in badminton", "answer":"Shuttlecock"},
  {"category":"SPORTS", "question":"Who won the Euros in 2021", "answer":"Italy"},
  {"category":"SPORTS", "question":"Is the top of the net higher in Tennis or Table Tennis", "answer":"Tennis"},
  {"category":"SPORTS", "question":"How high off the ground is a basketball hoop in feet", "answer":"10"},
  {"category":"SPORTS", "question":"How many people are on the pitch at the start of a football match", "answer":"23"},

  {"category":"ANIMALS", "question":"What is the name of the fastest land animal", "answer":"Cheetah"},
  {"category":"ANIMALS", "question":"What is the only mammal capable of sustained flight", "answer":"Bat"},
  {"category":"ANIMALS", "question":"From which animal do we get venison", "answer":"Deer"},
  {"category":"ANIMALS", "question":"What was the first mammal to be launched into space", "answer":"Monkey"},
  {"category":"ANIMALS", "question":"Which African-native mammal has the most powerful bite in the world", "answer":"Hippo"},
  {"category":"ANIMALS", "question":"What colour is a polar bear's skin", "answer":"Black"},

  {"category":"SPACE", "question":"What planet has the strongest gravitational pull", "answer":"Jupiter"},
  {"category":"SPACE", "question":"What is the hottest planet in our solar system as well as the Roman Goddess of Love", "answer":"Venus"},
  {"category":"SPACE", "question":"What is the closest major galaxy to the Milky Way", "answer":"Andromeda"},
  
  {"category":"CARS", "question":"What animal can be seen on the Porsche Logo", "answer":"Horse"},
  {"category":"CARS", "question":"Which sports car features in the Back To The Future trilogy", "answer":"DeLorean"},
  {"category":"CARS", "question":"How many rings are in the Audi logo", "answer":"4"},

  {"category":"BOARD GAMES", "question":"True/False: Monopoly banned in Spain?", "answer":"False"},
  {"category":"BOARD GAMES", "question":"How many ships does each player have in Battleship", "answer":"5"},
  {"category":"BOARD GAMES", "question":"Which chess piece cannot move backwards", "answer":"Pawn"},
  {"category":"BOARD GAMES", "question":"How many points is the letter J worth in Scrabble", "answer":"8"},

  {"category":"TECHNOLOGY", "question":"What does the term GPU stand for", "answer":"Graphical Processing Unit"},
  {"category":"TECHNOLOGY", "question":"What is the smallest type of data", "answer":"Bit"},
  {"category":"TECHNOLOGY", "question":"Which phone company created the messaging service BBM", "answer":"Blackberry"},
  {"category":"TECHNOLOGY", "question":"Name three operating systems", "answer":"Windows, Linux, MacOS, Android, Unix, iOS etc."},
  {"category":"TECHNOLOGY", "question":"What colour is the black box on commercial planes", "answer":"Orange"},
  {"category":"TECHNOLOGY", "question":"In what year was the first iPhone released", "answer":"2007"},

  {"category":"BUSINESS", "question":"What product did Amazon initially start out selling", "answer":"Books"},
  {"category":"BUSINESS", "question":"What car company produced cars for the Nazi party", "answer":"Volkswagen"},
  {"category":"BUSINESS", "question":"What company creates the soft drink Fanta", "answer":"Coca-Cola"},

  {"category":"LITERACY", "question":"What unit of measurement is 0.9144 metres", "answer":"Yard"},
  {"category":"LITERACY", "question":"What word comes before deck, recorder and measure", "answer":"Tape"},
  {"category":"LITERACY", "question":"What word shares its name with a rocket and a mythological God", "answer":"Apollo"},
  {"category":"LITERACY", "question":"What word comes before beam, spot and set", "answer":"Sun"},
  {"category":"LITERACY", "question":"What is the first month of the year to have 30 days", "answer":"April"},
  {"category":"LITERACY", "question":"What relationship is your mother's cousin's child to you", "answer":"Second Cousin"},
  {"category":"LITERACY", "question":"Spell rhythm", "answer":"R-H-Y-T-H-M"},
  {"category":"LITERACY", "question":"Other than Germany, whose official language is German", "answer":"Austria"},

  {"category":"YOUTUBE", "question":"What is the most disliked video on youtube", "answer":"Youtube Rewind 2016"},
  {"category":"YOUTUBE", "question":"What is the most viewed diss track of all time", "answer":"The Fall of Jake Paul"},
  {"category":"YOUTUBE", "question":"Name the most viewed music video that shares its name with a sea creature", "answer":"Baby Shark"},
  {"category":"YOUTUBE", "question":"Who is the most subscribed member of the Sidemen", "answer":"KSI"},
  
  {"category":"BOOKS", "question":"Which is the longest Harry Potter book", "answer":"Order of the Phoenix"},
  {"category":"BOOKS", "question":"What colour is the Mr Men character Mr Happy", "answer":"Yellow"},
  {"category":"BOOKS", "question":"The writer of the Hunger Games is called Suzanne: ", "answer":"Collins"},
  {"category":"BOOKS", "question":"What is the best selling book of all time", "answer":"The Bible"},
  
  {"category":"COMICS", "question":"Which DC villain played by Tom Hardy broke Batman's back", "answer":"Bane"},
  {"category":"COMICS", "question":"What superhero sidekick is known as the Boy Wonder", "answer":"Robin"},
  {"category":"COMICS", "question":"What was Superman's birth name before he took the name Clarke Kent", "answer":"Kal-EL"},
  {"category":"COMICS", "question":"Reed Richards is the alter ego of which superhero that leads a team of four", "answer":"Mr Fantastic"},

  {"category":"FILM", "question":"Who directed E.T", "answer":"Steven Spielberg"},
  {"category":"FILM", "question":"The Wet Bandits are the villains of which Christmas movie", "answer":"Home Alone"},
  {"category":"FILM", "question":"Who was the first Disney princess", "answer":"Snow White"},
  {"category":"FILM", "question":"Name the Dreamworks film starring British rats", "answer":"Flushed Away"},
  {"category":"FILM", "question":"Which 4 legged mammal is Shrek's best friend", "answer":"Donkey"},
  {"category":"FILM", "question":"The Minions first appeared in which movie", "answer":"Despicable Me"},
  {"category":"FILM", "question":"What is the best movie of 2022 so far", "answer":"Morbius"},
  {"category":"FILM", "question":"What is the highest grossing R rated movie of all time", "answer":"Joker"},

  {"category":"ANIME", "question":"Who is the main Jojo in JJBA part 3", "answer":"Jotaro Kujo"},
  {"category":"ANIME", "question":"What does Naruto want to become", "answer":"Hokage"},
  {"category":"ANIME", "question":"How many dragon balls are there", "answer":"7"},
  {"category":"ANIME", "question":"Which series revolves around the Elric brothers", "answer":"Fullmetal Alchemist"},
  {"category":"ANIME", "question":"Who killed Light in Death Note", "answer":"Ryuk"},

  {"category":"CLOTHING", "question":"What Ancient Roman garment is also an anagram of the word goat", "answer":"Ryuk"},

  {"category":"TELEVISION", "question":"Who is friends with Jesse Pinkman, Badger and Skinny Pete", "answer":"Combo"},
  {"category":"TELEVISION", "question":"What is the first name of Gus' late boyfriend", "answer":"Max"},
  {"category":"TELEVISION", "question":"Which three people founded the cartel in Breaking Bad", "answer":"Eladio, Hector and Bolsa"},
  {"category":"TELEVISION", "question":"In The Boys, what is the name of Homelander's son", "answer":"Ryan"},
  {"category":"TELEVISION", "question":"What was the first Pixar movie", "answer":"Toy Story"},
  {"category":"TELEVISION", "question":"You think this is bad? This? This:", "answer":"Chicanery"},
  {"category":"TELEVISION", "question":"Andrew Lincoln plays the main character of this AMC show", "answer":"The Walking Dead"},
  {"category":"TELEVISION", "question":"What was the first MCU Disney+ show", "answer":"WandaVision"},
  {"category":"TELEVISION", "question":"Cartman, Stan, Kyle and Kenny are from which animated show", "answer":"South Park"},
 
  {"category":"GAMING", "question":"Vice City and San Andreas are games from which franchise", "answer":"GTA"},
  {"category":"GAMING", "question":"Who drove the truck during the Fortnite Collision event", "answer":"Peely"},
  {"category":"GAMING", "question":"What colourful track is the final course on all Mario Kart games", "answer":"Rainbow Road"},
  {"category":"GAMING", "question":"Which French publishes the Assassins Creed games", "answer":"Ubisoft"},
  {"category":"GAMING", "question":"What is the highest selling video game console", "answer":"PS2"},
  {"category":"GAMING", "question":"What is the highest selling handheld video game console", "answer":"Nintendo DS"},
  {"category":"GAMING", "question":"What is the highest selling video game", "answer":"Minecraft"},
  {"category":"GAMING", "question":"Who is the blond, male default skin in Fortnite", "answer":"Jonesy"},
  {"category":"GAMING", "question":"Knuckles from Sonic is what animal?", "answer":"Echidna"},
  {"category":"GAMING", "question":"Who is the main character from the Zelda series?", "answer":"Link"},
  {"category":"GAMING", "question":"Who came first, Mario or Sonic?", "answer":"Mario"},
  {"category":"GAMING", "question":"The character of Mario first appeared in which other Nintendo character's game", "answer":"Donkey Kong"},
  
  {"category":"MATHS", "question":"What is the cube root of 1000", "answer":"10"},
  {"category":"MATHS", "question":"On what number is the decimal system based", "answer":"10"},
  {"category":"MATHS", "question":"What is 10 x 10 - 10", "answer":"90"},
  {"category":"MATHS", "question":"What is 7 squared", "answer":"49"},

  {"category":"HISTORY", "question":"In which decade did Neil Armstrong land on the moon", "answer":"60s"},
  {"category":"HISTORY", "question":"Who is known as the King of the Greek Gods ", "answer":"Zeus"},
  {"category":"HISTORY", "question":"What surname was adopted by the British royal family in 1917", "answer":"Windsor"},
  {"category":"HISTORY", "question":"How many US Presidents have been assassinated", "answer":"4"},
  {"category":"HISTORY", "question":"At the time of Julius Caesar, who ruled Egypt", "answer":"Cleopatra"},
  {"category":"HISTORY", "question":"What title was given to Ancient Egyptian rulers", "answer":"Pharaoh"},
  {"category":"HISTORY", "question":"What year did WW2 end", "answer":"1945"},

  {"category":"FOOD", "question":"What colour is the flesh of an avocado", "answer":"Green"},
  {"category":"FOOD", "question":"What type of nuts are used in marzipan", "answer":"Almonds"},
  {"category":"FOOD", "question":"What type of food is pitta", "answer":"Bread"},
  {"category":"FOOD", "question":"What is the food of the Gods in Greek Mythology,", "answer":"Ambrosia"},
  {"category":"FOOD", "question":"Is wholemeal bread brown or white", "answer":"Brown"},
  {"category":"FOOD", "question":"What fruit is named after its colour", "answer":"Orange"},

  {"category":"POLITICS", "question":"Who became Prime Minister of Canada in 2015", "answer":"Justin Trudeau"},
  {"category":"POLITICS", "question":"Who became the first Prime Minister of Cube in 1959", "answer":"Fidel Castro"},

  {"category":"DRINKS", "question":"How is a drinkS served when it is described as frappe", "answer":"With crushed ice"},
  {"category":"DRINKS", "question":"The 18th Amendment in the US Constitution was repealed in 1933. What did it ban", "answer":"Alcohol"},
  {"category":"DRINKS", "question":"James Bond's preferred drink of choice is a Vodka: ", "answer":"Martini"},
  {"category":"DRINKS", "question":"What spirit is Malibu made up of", "answer":"Rum"},
  {"category":"DRINKS", "question":"Juniper berries flavour which spirit", "answer":"Gin"},
  {"category":"DRINKS", "question":"Is Guinness vegan?", "answer":"Yes"},
  {"category":"DRINKS", "question":"Name the oldest fizzy soft drink, which shares its name with a type of fruit", "answer":"Dr Pepper"},

  {"category":"FANDOME", "question":"Including bots, how many members are in the server to the nearest 10", "answer":"70"},
  {"category":"FANDOME", "question":"After Doc, who was the first person to join The FanDome", "answer":"Batnerd"},
  {"category":"FANDOME", "question":"After Doc, who sent the first message into The FanDome", "answer":"Spring"},
  {"category":"FANDOME", "question":"In which month and year did TMU fall", "answer":"March 2021"},
  {"category":"FANDOME", "question":"Who is the highest ranked member on the Juniper bot", "answer":"Slushie"},
  {"category":"FANDOME", "question":"How many members level 25 or higher are from the UK", "answer":"5"},
  {"category":"FANDOME", "question":"What is Slushie's full name", "answer":"Sadhbh Molly Ryan"},
  {"category":"FANDOME", "question":"Who is the oldest active member", "answer":"Kalerteth"},
  {"category":"FANDOME", "question":"In which type of building did Henry Newman first have sex", "answer":"Tent"},
  {"category":"FANDOME", "question":"Noah Roach belongs to what ancient clan", "answer":"Shinklebottom"},
  {"category":"FANDOME", "question":"Where was I born", "answer":"Luton"},
  {"category":"FANDOME", "question":"In what year did British artist Olly Murs die", "answer":"2019"}
]